Finding Aid for the Larry Gelbart Papers PASC.0022
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects
  - Stage Projects
    - GULLIVER - Publicity packets from Soundwings,Inc. 1987. - Program from The Philharmonic Orchestra of Yale, October 10, 1986. (Box 154, Folder 5)
      Publicity packets from Soundwings,Inc. 1987. - Program from The Philharmonic Orchestra of Yale, October 10, 1986.
    - GULLIVER - Clippings and publicity pieces/drafts, 1986-1987 re records release of "GULLIVER - " by Soundwings, Inc. - Kodak booklet with photographs from the 1970 GULLIVER - 's Travels production (Frow and Kenny). (Box 154, Folder 6)
      Clippings and publicity pieces/drafts, 1986-1987 re records release of "GULLIVER - " by Soundwings, Inc. - Kodak booklet with photographs from the 1970 GULLIVER - 's Travels production (Frow and Kenny).
    - GULLIVER - Monologues: " A Voyage to Liliput" dated 9/24/85 & 7/5/85. - "A Voyage to Brobdingnag", dated rev. 9/13/85 & 9/24/85. (Box 154, Folder 7)
      Monologues: " A Voyage to Liliput" dated 9/24/85 & 7/5/85. - "A Voyage to Brobdingnag", dated rev. 9/13/85 & 9/24/85.
    - GULLIVER - Clipping from Kodak photography magazine, January, 1970. Article, "Science and Our Century," with handwritten note: LAPUTA. Photocopied research materials. (Box 155, Folder 1)
      Clipping from Kodak photography magazine, January, 1970. Article, "Science and Our Century," with handwritten note: LAPUTA. Photocopied research materials.
    - GULLIVER - Notes: "Casting", "Notes on discussion Act 1, 5/29/70", "Notes by Sean Kenny", "Notes-L.B., 3/6/70", "Choreographer, Don Redlich. - MS notes re staging, 18 pages. - Misc. - Playbill: Mermais Theatre. Typed notes, "Before Houynhnms," 3p. (Box 155, Folder 1)
      Notes: "Casting", "Notes on discussion Act 1, 5/29/70", "Notes by Sean Kenny", "Notes-L.B., 3/6/70", "Choreographer, Don Redlich. - MS notes re staging, 18 pages. - Misc. - Playbill: Mermais Theatre. Typed notes, "Before Houynhnms," 3p.
    - GULLIVER - "Notes taken from tape recording of meeting at Reece Mews, 1st February, 1970". Present: Larry Gelbart, Sean Kenny, and Lionel Bart. 44 pages. (Box 155, Folder 2)
      "Notes taken from tape recording of meeting at Reece Mews, 1st February, 1970". Present: Larry Gelbart, Sean Kenny, and Lionel Bart. 44 pages.
    - HALLOWEEN - Tragic-Farce in three acts titled "Saltpeter in the Rhubarb" by Sidney Michaels, copyright 1965. (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Tragic-Farce in three acts titled "Saltpeter in the Rhubarb" by Sidney Michaels, copyright 1965.
    - HALLOWEEN - "An Original Musical Play". Book & lyrics by Sidney Michaels, music by Mitch Leigh, to be staged by Albert Marre. 2 copies, n.d., one annotated. (Property of Albert W. Selden, New York). (Box 32, Folder 2)
      "An Original Musical Play". Book & lyrics by Sidney Michaels, music by Mitch Leigh, to be staged by Albert Marre. 2 copies, n.d., one annotated. (Property of Albert W. Selden, New York).
    - HALLOWEEN - Scripts, dated 09/15/71. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Scripts, dated 09/15/71.
    - HALLOWEEN - Incomplete script, many pages with changes and additions. Revisions dated September, 16, 24, 1972. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Incomplete script, many pages with changes and additions. Revisions dated September, 16, 24, 1972.
    - HALLOWEEN - Scripts, incorporating changes September and October 1992. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Scripts, incorporating changes September and October 1992.
    - HALLOWEEN - Scripts, two different versions. - Loose pages of revisions for Act 1 and Act II. Some pages dated August 29, 1972. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Scripts, two different versions. - Loose pages of revisions for Act 1 and Act II. Some pages dated August 29, 1972.
    - HALLOWEEN - Playbill, 1972, New Hope Pennsylvania. Presented by The State Theatre of Pennsylvania. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Playbill, 1972, New Hope Pennsylvania. Presented by The State Theatre of Pennsylvania.
    - HANGING ON - Script titled "Nothing But Candy", by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum), handwritten, incl. typed pages, first draft, 2 acts, n.d. - Scripts, handwritten and typed pages, mainly Act 1. n.d. (Box 155, Folder 11)
      Script titled "Nothing But Candy", by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum), handwritten, incl. typed pages, first draft, 2 acts, n.d. - Scripts, handwritten and typed pages, mainly Act 1. n.d.
    - HANGING ON - Script by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. Act I only. No date. 49 pages. (Box 162, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. Act I only. No date. 49 pages.
    - HANGING ON - Script titled "Nothing but Candy". A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. 'Hollywood is like having nothing to eat but candy,' W. Somerset Maugham." Draft, March 1 1983, 2 acts, annotated. 82 p. (Box 162, Folder 5)
      Script titled "Nothing but Candy". A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. 'Hollywood is like having nothing to eat but candy,' W. Somerset Maugham." Draft, March 1 1983, 2 acts, annotated. 82 p.
    - HANGING ON - Script titled "Nothing But Candy". A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum, 'Hollywood is like having nothing to eat but candy,' W. Somerset Maugham." March 31 1983, 2 acts, 93 p. (Box 162, Folder 6)
      Script titled "Nothing But Candy". A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum, 'Hollywood is like having nothing to eat but candy,' W. Somerset Maugham." March 31 1983, 2 acts, 93 p.
    - HANGING ON - Script titled "Nothing but Candy". A play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. 'Hollywood is like having nothing to eat but candy,' W. Somerset Maugham." May 15 1983. Typed original. 2 acts. 93 p. (Box 162, Folder 7)
      Script titled "Nothing but Candy". A play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. 'Hollywood is like having nothing to eat but candy,' W. Somerset Maugham." May 15 1983. Typed original. 2 acts. 93 p.
    - HANGING ON - Cover letter from E.G. to L.G. regarding errata (1985). Script [no title page], n.d., 2 acts, 72 p. - Act one only, [no title page], n.d., 49 p. (Box 162, Folder 8)
      Cover letter from E.G. to L.G. regarding errata (1985). Script [no title page], n.d., 2 acts, 72 p. - Act one only, [no title page], n.d., 49 p.
    - HANGING ON - A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. Draft, April 3 1985, annotated. 2 acts. 91 p. (Box 163, Folder 1)
      A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. Draft, April 3 1985, annotated. 2 acts. 91 p.
    - HANGING ON - A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. Was titled "Nothing but Candy." Old titled is marked over with "HANGING ON - ." Draft, January 15 1985. Annotated. 2 acts. 105 p. (Box 163, Folder 2)
      A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum. Was titled "Nothing but Candy." Old titled is marked over with "HANGING ON - ." Draft, January 15 1985. Annotated. 2 acts. 105 p.
    - HANGING ON - A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum, April 15 1985, 2 acts, 92 p. - 2 sets of revision pages for act I, 6/5/89 (p. 2-6) & 5/30/89 (p. 2-4). (Box 163, Folder 3)
      A Play by Larry Gelbart and Everett Greenbaum, April 15 1985, 2 acts, 92 p. - 2 sets of revision pages for act I, 6/5/89 (p. 2-6) & 5/30/89 (p. 2-4).
    - HANGING ON - Letter from Everett Greenbaum to Larry Gelbart regarding logo for the production. n.d. Logo is designed by Billie Greenbaum. Includes logo design (2 sizes), 1 page. (Box 163, Folder 4)
      Letter from Everett Greenbaum to Larry Gelbart regarding logo for the production. n.d. Logo is designed by Billie Greenbaum. Includes logo design (2 sizes), 1 page.
    - HANGING ON - "The Story of a Survivor." MS notes in rough outline form. No date. 2 pages. (Box 164, Folder 11)
      "The Story of a Survivor." MS notes in rough outline form. No date. 2 pages.
    - HOT SPOT (Stage Project) - Script, handwritten by Larry Gelbart, 16 pages, n.d. - Typed scripts, n.d., 12 pages, 2 copies. (Box 155, Folder 7)
      Script, handwritten by Larry Gelbart, 16 pages, n.d. - Typed scripts, n.d., 12 pages, 2 copies.
    - JEROME ROBBINS' BROADWAY (Box 180, Folder 15)
      Contract material with BMG, 2/12/89. - Correspondence, 7/90-7/91. - Playbill, Imperial Theater, Vol. 89, No. 1, 1/89.
    - JUMP - A play by Larry Gelbart, (2 acts), n.d., 3 copies, all with annotations. (Box 39, Folder 1)
      A play by Larry Gelbart, (2 acts), n.d., 3 copies, all with annotations.
    - JUMP - A play by Larry Gelbart, (2 acts), n.d., 103 p. Marked property of "The Open Space Theatre", London, England. (Box 39, Folder 2)
      A play by Larry Gelbart, (2 acts), n.d., 103 p. Marked property of "The Open Space Theatre", London, England.
    - JUMP - A Play by Larry Gelbart, (2 acts), n.d. One version 98 pages, one version Act I, 54 pages, Act II, 39 pages. Both marked "Ziegler-Ross, Inc., Los Angeles." (Box 39, Folder 3)
      A Play by Larry Gelbart, (2 acts), n.d. One version 98 pages, one version Act I, 54 pages, Act II, 39 pages. Both marked "Ziegler-Ross, Inc., Los Angeles."
    - JUMP - Production and directorial notes re changes after opening, dated 08/29/71. (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Production and directorial notes re changes after opening, dated 08/29/71.
    - JUMP - Playbills for productions 1) Theatre Royal, Nottingham, England, dated 08/16/71. 2) The Queens Theatre, London, 1975. Incl. publicity flyers for Queens Theatre. (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Playbills for productions 1) Theatre Royal, Nottingham, England, dated 08/16/71. 2) The Queens Theatre, London, 1975. Incl. publicity flyers for Queens Theatre.
    - JUMP - Correspondence, 1970 through 1971. 1) Preproduction correspondence with Charles Marowitz (Open Space Theatre, London), 25 items. 2) Congratulatory telegrams from friends re opening. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Correspondence, 1970 through 1971. 1) Preproduction correspondence with Charles Marowitz (Open Space Theatre, London), 25 items. 2) Congratulatory telegrams from friends re opening.
    - JUMP - Manuscript of the play, in 2 acts, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 5)
      Manuscript of the play, in 2 acts, n.d.
    - JUMP - Clippings re London production, 1971. (Box 42, Folder 6)
      Clippings re London production, 1971.
    - JUMP - A Play by Larry Gelbart, 93 p., copious annotations, marked "Redstacks, London". - Pages 78 through 93 handwritten. (Box 42, Folder 9)
      A Play by Larry Gelbart, 93 p., copious annotations, marked "Redstacks, London". - Pages 78 through 93 handwritten.
    - LITTLE ME - Book by Neil Simon, music by Cy Coleman, lyrics by Carolyn Leigh, based on "LITTLE ME" by Patrick Dennis. Annotated. No date. - Includes Prop Plot, 8 pages. (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Book by Neil Simon, music by Cy Coleman, lyrics by Carolyn Leigh, based on "LITTLE ME" by Patrick Dennis. Annotated. No date. - Includes Prop Plot, 8 pages.
    - LITTLE ME - Book by Neil Simon, music by Cy Coleman, lyrics by Carolyn Leigh, based on "LITTLE ME" by Patrick Dennis. Marked "Final script, English version", "Enid Lowe." No date. (Box 59, Folder 2)
      Book by Neil Simon, music by Cy Coleman, lyrics by Carolyn Leigh, based on "LITTLE ME" by Patrick Dennis. Marked "Final script, English version", "Enid Lowe." No date.
    - MASTERGATE - Handwritten and typed revisions. - Annotated typed script, 74 pages, revised 1/12/88. (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Handwritten and typed revisions. - Annotated typed script, 74 pages, revised 1/12/88.
    - MASTERGATE - Publicity correspondence, issued by the Golden Group, representing the Cirterion Center production, 1989. (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Publicity correspondence, issued by the Golden Group, representing the Cirterion Center production, 1989.
    - MASTERGATE - Playbills/flyers: American Repertory Theatre (Boston), incl. and ticket stubs, 1989. - Flyers for Berkeshire Public Theatre (Pittsfield MA), 1990. (Box 48, Folder 5)
      Playbills/flyers: American Repertory Theatre (Boston), incl. and ticket stubs, 1989. - Flyers for Berkeshire Public Theatre (Pittsfield MA), 1990.
    - MASTERGATE - Clippings regarding the Washington and New York productions, 1989 - 1990. approx. 200 items. (Box 48, Folder 6)
      Clippings regarding the Washington and New York productions, 1989 - 1990. approx. 200 items.
    - MASTERGATE - Script, reviews, and photographs (6 b/w) of the University California Irvine presentation, in August 1992. (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Script, reviews, and photographs (6 b/w) of the University California Irvine presentation, in August 1992.
    - MASTERGATE - Correspondence re - University California Irvine stage production. Dated Spring 1992. Includes some legal issues re Showtime production interfering with UCI production. (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Correspondence re - University California Irvine stage production. Dated Spring 1992. Includes some legal issues re Showtime production interfering with UCI production.
    - MASTERGATE - Correspondence re various versions for different staged performances. Dated 1990-1992. (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Correspondence re various versions for different staged performances. Dated 1990-1992.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Play on Words." Book by Larry Gelbart, dated 11/01/90. Includes excerpts printed in magazines. (Box 52, Folder 6)
      "A Play on Words." Book by Larry Gelbart, dated 11/01/90. Includes excerpts printed in magazines.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 2/88. (Box 52, Folder 8)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 2/88.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two copies, both dated 3/88. Both heavily by differently annotated. (Box 52, Folder 9)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two copies, both dated 3/88. Both heavily by differently annotated.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 4/88. (Box 52, Folder 10)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 4/88.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. First draft, dated 05/15/88. (Box 54, Folder 1)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. First draft, dated 05/15/88.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two copies, dated 06/01/88, one heavily annotated. (Box 54, Folder 2)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two copies, dated 06/01/88, one heavily annotated.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two copies - Dated 11/16/88, marked "Dear Mom this is a first draft, there will be many changes." - Proof copy, dated 12/01/88 (annotated). (Box 54, Folder 3)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two copies - Dated 11/16/88, marked "Dear Mom this is a first draft, there will be many changes." - Proof copy, dated 12/01/88 (annotated).
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two scripts. 1) Dated 12/07/88 2) Dated 12/23/88, marked "Please Save for Larry Gelbart, The Charles Hotel, ..." (Box 54, Folder 4)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two scripts. 1) Dated 12/07/88 2) Dated 12/23/88, marked "Please Save for Larry Gelbart, The Charles Hotel, ..."
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two scripts, dated 12/28/88, one with copious annotations, 60 and 74 pages respectively. (Box 54, Folder 5)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two scripts, dated 12/28/88, one with copious annotations, 60 and 74 pages respectively.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two copies, dated 01/23/89. Annotated. (Box 54, Folder 6)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Two copies, dated 01/23/89. Annotated.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart, dated 02/08/89, marked "A.R.T. version, 1st Performance". - "A Play on Words", by Larry Gelbart, dated 02/08/89. (Box 55, Folder 1)
      "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart, dated 02/08/89, marked "A.R.T. version, 1st Performance". - "A Play on Words", by Larry Gelbart, dated 02/08/89.
    - MASTERGATE - "A Congressional Hearing" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 08/01/89. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - MASTERGATE - "A Play on Words" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 10/12/89. (Box 55, Folder 3)
      "A Play on Words" by Larry Gelbart. Dated 10/12/89.
    - MASTERGATE - Incomplete script, pages 1-52, heavily annotated. - Incomplete script, pp. 25-92, annotated. - Several groups of pages of revisions. (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Incomplete script, pages 1-52, heavily annotated. - Incomplete script, pp. 25-92, annotated. - Several groups of pages of revisions.
    - MASTERGATE - Script, pages 2-62, untitled, n.d. - Typed notes titled "Hollywood, D.C," dated 01/02/88, 10 pages. - Revised pages, some dated 2/3, 2/4, 2/6, 5/23/89. (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Script, pages 2-62, untitled, n.d. - Typed notes titled "Hollywood, D.C," dated 01/02/88, 10 pages. - Revised pages, some dated 2/3, 2/4, 2/6, 5/23/89.
    - MASTERGATE - Congratulatory notes and telegrams regarding the New York opening, 10/89. Approximately 100 items. (Box 55, Folder 7)
      Congratulatory notes and telegrams regarding the New York opening, 10/89. Approximately 100 items.
    - MASTERGATE - Correspondence regarding contract negotiations for potential theatre rights, publishing rights, and movie rights. Includes xerox copies of checks paid for movie rights. Dates range in 1989. (Box 55, Folder 8)
      Correspondence regarding contract negotiations for potential theatre rights, publishing rights, and movie rights. Includes xerox copies of checks paid for movie rights. Dates range in 1989.
    - MASTERGATE - Articles in Theater Week, Oct. 16, 1989, The Nation, Nov. 6, 1989, - Acrostic in Harpers, February 1990. (Missing -10/24/98). (Box 55, Folder 9)
      Articles in Theater Week, Oct. 16, 1989, The Nation, Nov. 6, 1989, - Acrostic in Harpers, February 1990. (Missing -10/24/98).
    - MASTERGATE - Copies of publicity drawings, 8 items. Includes note from Gene Wolsk (artist). (Box 55, Folder 10)
      Copies of publicity drawings, 8 items. Includes note from Gene Wolsk (artist).
    - MASTERGATE - Correspondence and list of inquiries regarding the publication and future production of the play, 1989/90. - The Golden Group, Advertising Copy: copy lines for print, tv, radio, 7 pages, 1989. (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Correspondence and list of inquiries regarding the publication and future production of the play, 1989/90. - The Golden Group, Advertising Copy: copy lines for print, tv, radio, 7 pages, 1989.
    - MASTERGATE - Production items: Rehearsal schedules (9/26/89), rehearsal calendar, (8/27/89 - 10/7/89), casting lists (Simon and Kumin Casting), company contact sheet (9/30/89). (Box 55, Folder 12)
      Production items: Rehearsal schedules (9/26/89), rehearsal calendar, (8/27/89 - 10/7/89), casting lists (Simon and Kumin Casting), company contact sheet (9/30/89).
    - MASTERGATE - "The Found Poetry of Lt. Col. Oliver L. North as found and compiled by John W. Hart, III". And Books, South Bend, Indiana. 28 pages. (Box 55, Folder 14)
      "The Found Poetry of Lt. Col. Oliver L. North as found and compiled by John W. Hart, III". And Books, South Bend, Indiana. 28 pages.
    - MASTERGATE - "Larry Gelbart on MASTERGATE - " by Arthur Holmberg (interview). - Biographies of Larry Gelbart, Michael Engler, Joseph Daly, and Steve Hofvendahl. Includes expanded biography of Engler. (Box 55, Folder 15)
      "Larry Gelbart on MASTERGATE - " by Arthur Holmberg (interview). - Biographies of Larry Gelbart, Michael Engler, Joseph Daly, and Steve Hofvendahl. Includes expanded biography of Engler.
    - MASTERGATE - Article about stage production, by Larry Gelbart. Three drafts, each with coversheet addressed to Andrea Chapin. (Box 55, Folder 16)
      Article about stage production, by Larry Gelbart. Three drafts, each with coversheet addressed to Andrea Chapin.
    - MIDWAY - "One Minute Play" (4 pages), submitted to American Repertory Theatre and Institute for Advanced Theatre Training, Cambridge, MA, April 1990. (Fundraising event). (Box 10, Folder 7)
      "One Minute Play" (4 pages), submitted to American Repertory Theatre and Institute for Advanced Theatre Training, Cambridge, MA, April 1990. (Fundraising event).
    - MUPPETS IN CONCERT - "Some Thoughts on 'The Muppets in Concert," 1973, 4 p. -Sketches for Muppets and choreography (4). (Box 164, Folder 2)
      "Some Thoughts on 'The Muppets in Concert," 1973, 4 p. -Sketches for Muppets and choreography (4).
    - MY LA - Reviews for opening approx. 20 items, circa 1951. (Box 143, Folder 4)
      Reviews for opening approx. 20 items, circa 1951.
    - MY LA - Congratulatory telegrams regarding opening (9), dated December 7 1950. - Playbill for the Forum Theatre - Oversized program from the Forum (2). - Call for investors in MY LA Ltd. (Box 143, Folder 5)
      Congratulatory telegrams regarding opening (9), dated December 7 1950. - Playbill for the Forum Theatre - Oversized program from the Forum (2). - Call for investors in MY LA Ltd.
    - MY LA - Scenes and lyrics. Approx. 200 p. circa 1951. Some annotations. (Box 143, Folder 6)
      Scenes and lyrics. Approx. 200 p. circa 1951. Some annotations.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Handwritten draft by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart (Gelbart's handwriting). First draft, January 18, 1986. (Box 103, Folder 8)
      Handwritten draft by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart (Gelbart's handwriting). First draft, January 18, 1986.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Handwritten draft. Dated February 1987. (Box 103, Folder 9)
      Handwritten draft. Dated February 1987.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Partial script. Various dates from October to December 1987. Heavily annotated. (Box 107, Folder 9)
      Partial script. Various dates from October to December 1987. Heavily annotated.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Scripts. A Musical by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart. Labeled "Final Performance Version." Dated 11/29/87. (Box 107, Folder 10)
      Scripts. A Musical by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart. Labeled "Final Performance Version." Dated 11/29/87.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Partial Script. Dated December 1987 - January 1988. Includes a letter (01/14/88) explaining revisions to Act II. (Box 108, Folder 1)
      Partial Script. Dated December 1987 - January 1988. Includes a letter (01/14/88) explaining revisions to Act II.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Script. A Musical Comedy by Maury Yetson and Larry Gelbart. Dated, 01/30/88. (Box 108, Folder 2)
      Script. A Musical Comedy by Maury Yetson and Larry Gelbart. Dated, 01/30/88.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Script. A Musical Comedy by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart. Annotated. Dated March 20, 1988. (Box 108, Folder 3)
      Script. A Musical Comedy by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart. Annotated. Dated March 20, 1988.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Script. A Musical Comedy by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart. Dated May 1, 1988. (Box 108, Folder 4)
      Script. A Musical Comedy by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart. Dated May 1, 1988.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Script. A Musical Comedy by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart. Draft, annotated, Sept 1 & Nov 10, 1988. Marked: Rehearsal, Nov 19 - Opening Date Dec 19 - Closing Jan 18. (Box 108, Folder 5)
      Script. A Musical Comedy by Maury Yeston and Larry Gelbart. Draft, annotated, Sept 1 & Nov 10, 1988. Marked: Rehearsal, Nov 19 - Opening Date Dec 19 - Closing Jan 18.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Draft of Act One only. Dated November 5, 1988. Marked: "Look at all Maylis speeches." Few annotations. (Box 108, Folder 6)
      Draft of Act One only. Dated November 5, 1988. Marked: "Look at all Maylis speeches." Few annotations.
    - ONE TWO THREE FOUR FIVE - Script, dated 11/11/88. Marked: "Mom, It Keeps changing all the time - but this is the version we've just gone into rehearsal with - Love, L.G., 11/21/88." (Box 108, Folder 7)